broadcom.com 2015-11-19

# Broadcom Privacy Policy | Broadcom

**Effective Nov. 17, 2015**

This privacy policy describes the information that Broadcom and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, "Broadcom" "we," "our", "us" or the "Company") collects about you, how we use and protect this information, and the choices you can make about how we use this information. This policy applies to information, including Personal Information, collected about you by Broadcom in different methods, including via the [www.broadcom.com](http://www.broadcom.com/) website. It also explains how cookies and similar technologies are used by us and third parties.

"Personal Information" means any information or set of information that identifies or could be used by or on behalf of Broadcom to identify an individual, such as the individual's name, address, email address, affiliated organization or company name, phone number, employer/profession or other specific types of personal information. Personal Information does not include information that is encoded or anonymized, or publicly available information that has not been combined with non-public Personal Information.

Broadcom respects individual privacy and values the confidence of its customers, employees, consumers, business partners and others. 

Broadcom has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website, www.broadcom.com, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the website or the Customer Support Portal.

Broadcom complies with the U.S. - E.U. Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union member countries in relation to its human resource administration and management. Broadcom has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program and to view Broadcom's certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy or complaints regarding our compliance with the Safe Harbor, you should first contact us (our contact information is set forth below). If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may raise your complaint with TRUSTe by [Internet here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request), fax to 415-520-3420, or mail to TRUSTe Safe Harbor Compliance Dept., [click for mailing address](https://www.truste.com/about-truste/contact-us/). If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of the company (Broadcom), the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the company. For information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe's dispute resolution process, click [here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the addresses listed above. The TRUSTe dispute resolution process shall be conducted in English.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Broadcom may collect information about our customers, investors, business partners, vendors, job applicants, prospective employees and others in a variety of ways, including through personal contact, via our website and the internet, over the telephone, through correspondence with our employees and their attendance at industry events, when you use our products or services, when you apply for a job, and through third parties or other sources, where permitted by law. The personal information collected by us, or on our behalf, shall be limited to those details necessary for the purposes identified to you unless these are obvious to you or within your reasonable expectation. In general, we collect, use, and disclose information for the following purposes: to provide the products and services you request; to tell you about other products and services offered by Broadcom; to manage our sites and services; to administer and process any request for information or job application; to comply with our ethical, regulatory and legal obligations or requirements, including compliance with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process, or for the purposes of a government or regulatory investigation; or to protect or defend the rights or property of Broadcom.

In the event that we acquire an entity (such as through a merger or acquisition), we may use and/or disclose Personal Information of prospective employees to third parties in connection with the proposed transaction for the purposes of evaluating and/or performing the proposed transaction, and you consent to such disclosure. These purposes may include, for example, receiving advice on whether to proceed or continue with the transaction, fulfilling any reporting or audit requirements to such parties, and/or disclosing Personal Information as part of concluding a sale or transfer of assets. In the event a transaction is not concluded, we will require, by contract, any third parties not to use or disclose Personal Information in any manner whatsoever for any purpose, and to return or destroy such Personal Information.

In general, you can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information. However, Broadcom will collect, store, and/or use Personal Information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, or other information, when you voluntarily submit it to us - for example, when you request information about our products or when you submit an employment application online. We may use this Personal Information to respond to your requests for information or to contact you.

Personal Information may be disclosed in limited circumstances, including, but not limited to, legal process or for the purposes of a government investigation, to protect and defend the rights or property of Broadcom, or in an emergency threatening an individual's life, health, or security. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

We rely on third-party service providers to perform a variety of services on our behalf. Examples include HR recruiting, an email service provider, and investor portals on our site. In so doing, we may need to share your Personal Information with them. We provide our service providers with only the Personal Information they need to perform their services and we require that they protect this information and not use it for any other purpose. Except under the circumstances described above, Broadcom will not sell, rent, share, trade or disclose Personal Information to any third party for promotional purposes without your permission. We may supplement your personal information with information from third parties.

It is important to note that some or all of your Personal Information provided to third party service providers may be held by them in countries other than your own, including in particular the United States. You acknowledge and understand that your Personal Information will be subject to the applicable laws of each such jurisdiction, which may not provide for the same protection as your country of residence.

We use and disclose Personal Information only for the purposes that we have disclosed to you (unless these are obvious or within your reasonable expectation or otherwise permitted by law).

You can subscribe to receive email updates on our website. To unsubscribe from these updates, please return to the "Email Alert Subscription" page and unsubscribe or click on the link in the email. We also may send service related emails from which you cannot unsubscribe.

If you use a public forum on this website, you should be aware that any Personal Information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. To request removal of your Personal Information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacy-list@broadcom.com](mailto:privacy-list@broadcom.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personal Information, in which case we will let you know that we are unable to do so and the reasons why we are unable to do so.

The profile you create on our website may be publically accessible unless you indicate otherwise. You may change the privacy settings of your profile through your account portal.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit our website. Broadcom uses this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. Your friend may contact us at [privacy-list@broadcom.com](mailto:privacy-list@broadcom.com) to request that we remove his/her information from our database.

### Cookies and similar technologies

Through our use of cookies, web beacons, gifs, local storage, or other similar technologies, Broadcom may automatically collect information relating to such matters as: 

  * the total number of visits to this website,
  * the number of visitors to each page of this website,
  * the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of our visitors,
  * to distinguish you from other users of our website, and
  * the time spent on this website.

We may use this information, which is collected and remains in aggregate form, to understand how our visitors use this website so that we can provide you with a good experience when you browse our website, and also to improve the website. We may also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and for purposes of system administration. From time to time, we may share such aggregated information, which does not identify any individual, with our agents, business partners, consultants, or other third parties.

We gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

Cookies are text files stored on a user's computer hard drive containing information about the user and are used by most major websites. Cookies can enable us to track the interests of our users to enhance their experience on this website and to deliver content specific to a user's interests. We may place a cookie in the browser file of your computer when you visit this website. Third parties also place cookies on our website and the data is only collected in the aggregate.

You may delete or block cookies by activating the setting on your web browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. Although you may still use this website without the cookie, some parts of the website may not work properly for you.

If you would like further information about managing and disabling cookies, you can refer to your browser's help section or user guide. Alternatively, the Interactive Advertising Bureau has produced a guide (see [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)) which explains how cookies work and can be managed.

Broadcom is assessing available technology to respond to "do-not-track" browser signals; however, this website currently does not support those web browser settings.

We and our affiliates, analytics or service providers use technologies such as cookies, scripts, and tags to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregate basis. We also use software from Google Analytics for internal analytics that employs a software technology called "clear gifs" (which are also known as Web Beacons/ tracking pixels).

Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which, as discussed above, are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to users' Personal Information.

We use Google Analytics to collect information in an anonymous form about how visitors use the website, including the number of visitors to the website, where visitors have come to the website from, and the pages they visited. This information helps us better manage content on our website by informing us what content is effective. For more information about Google's privacy policy, please visit <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/>

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity use Local Storage (HTML5) to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. 

**PLEASE NOTE THAT BY USING THE WEBSITE WITHOUT BLOCKING COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES, YOU ARE EXPRESSLY CONSENTING TO THEIR USE AS DESCRIBED HEREIN.**

### Social Media Widgets

Our website includes social media features (such as the Facebook "Like" button), widgets (such as the "Share this" button), or interactive mini-programs that run on our website (collectively "Features"). These Features may collect your IP address and information on the page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Features to function properly. These Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the third party company providing them.

### Single Sign-On

You can log into the career section of our website using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share with us certain Personal Information, such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign-up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on our website to your social media profile page to share with others within your network.

### Minors

Broadcom does not knowingly collect or use Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13, nor do we market this website to anyone under the age of 13.

### Information Transfer and Storage

Your Personal Information may be transferred to, stored, and/or processed in the United States and/or other countries with different levels of privacy protection than are applicable in your country. When we do so, we transfer information in compliance with applicable data protection laws. We also take steps to protect Personal Information in the country in which it is stored or to which it is transferred. We have procedures and controls to help ensure the protection of Personal Information. Your Personal Information may also be processed by staff in the United States working for us or for one of our related companies, affiliates or suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of support services. By submitting your Personal Information via our website, you agree to any such transfers, storage or other processing.

Please note that if you are located in the European Union (EU), you expressly acknowledge that transfers of your Personal Information to countries outside of the EU may not benefit from the same level of protection as they do within the EU. 

We adhere to the EU Data Privacy Directive, as well as the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program, in relation to our human resource administration and management. For more information concerning the transfer of information relating to Broadcom personnel to other countries, please see our Safe Harbor Privacy Policy at <http://www.broadcom.com/docs/company/Safe_Harbor_Privacy_Policy.pdf>.

We will retain your information for as long as any accounts you may have are active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Subject to any applicable business, legal, or regulatory requirements, we securely destroy, erase or de-identify Personal Information when it is no longer required to fulfill our services to you or to enforce our rights or meet our obligations. 

### Access

Where allowed by law, you may request access to Personal Information that Broadcom holds about you by sending an email to [privacy-list@broadcom.com](mailto:privacy-list@broadcom.com). Broadcom will process that request in accordance with applicable local laws and our policies and procedures for dealing with such requests. Where allowed by law, Broadcom will also take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate or incomplete. Broadcom will respond to this request within 30 business days

There may be circumstances where we are unable to provide access to your personal information. We may deny or restrict access for legally permissible reasons, such as situations where the information contains references to other individuals and is not reasonably severable, or where it cannot be disclosed for legal, security, or commercial proprietary reasons. We will advise you of any reason for denying or restricting an access request.

### Security

We are committed to keeping Personal Information secure, and have implemented generally accepted industry standards of technical, administrative, organizational and physical procedures to protect Personal Information against unauthorized or unlawful processing of Personal Information and against accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, Personal Information. We also limit access to Personal Information to those who have a business need for access. When we provide your Personal Information to controllers or processors, including service providers, we require those companies to protect the information and not to use the information for any other purpose.

Nevertheless, although we have tried to create a secured and reliable website, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from this website cannot be guaranteed. We urge you to exercise caution when conveying Personal Information over the Internet. When disclosing any Personal Information, you should remain mindful that such information might be accessible by the public and, consequently, may be collected and used by others without your consent. You should also recognize that your use of the Internet and this website is solely at your own risk.

### Links

As a convenience to you, Broadcom may provide links from this website to other websites maintained by independent third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of independent third parties and once you leave the Broadcom website, this privacy policy will no longer apply. We encourage you to be aware when you leave this website, and to read the privacy policies of any other websites that you may visit.

Links to other websites are provided for informational purposes only and do not constitute endorsements of those other websites. Broadcom is not responsible for the content of links or third-party websites and does not make any representation regarding their content or accuracy. Your use of third-party websites is at your own risk.

### Amendment

This Policy may be amended from time to time.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the Broadcom home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.

### Notice to California Residents

Subject to certain limits under California Civil Code § 1798.83, California residents may ask us to provide them with (i) a list of certain categories of personal information that we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, and (ii) the identity of those third parties. To make this request, California residents may contact us as specified in the Contact Us section below. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding our privacy practices or this privacy policy, or would like to review or update your Personal Information, you may contact us at the following address: Global Privacy Officer, 5300 California Ave, Irvine, CA 92617 or send us an email at [privacy-list@broadcom.com](mailto:privacy-list@broadcom.com).
